Wait, Makabe! What are you doing?!
Then there's you!
Even if this is all just a
giant misunderstanding,
I can't let your current ugly
personality off the hook!
Ug—
So really...
If you're gonna go out with someone like him...
Go out with the real...
Go out with me instead!
#5 "So We Became a Couple"
Don't think I'm gonna take this lying down,
you shallow piece of shit who's
only got his face going for him.
Who are you calling shallow?!
You've been popular enough!
You're just pissed because
Aki-chan won't look your way!
That's not what this is about!
I won't let some popular guy use
Aki-chan for his stupid pride!
A popular guy's pride?
If I had anything like that,
none of this would have...
I've never been popular.
What? Give me a break with your fake humility!
It's the truth.
My earliest memories were of me
being bullied for being the fat kid.
My classmates always mocked me.
And then...
I ran into that arrogant little
girl's yard, and she saved me.
Masa...mune?
Huh?
Makabe Masa...
Masamune?
That's right.
The fat kid who ran away from your
place eight years ago wasn't Gasou.
It was me.
Qui...
Quit lying! That's a total fabrication!
Aki-chan! Are you actually
taking this guy seriously?!
Don't you remember how many
times he made you cry?
Who are you gonna believe? Me or him?!
Kanetsugu...
That's right! That's the right choice!
Exactly, Aki-chan!
No, that's not what I'm saying... Why do you...
have cleavage?
Cleavage?
Er, it's just... I never mentioned it.
I'm still the head of my household.
Oh, I think the hospital is calling me.
Excuse me now!
You're... Masamune?
I said I was, didn't I?
How are we supposed to act now?!
Seriously, I can't believe
how oblivious you are.
So you're into girls now?
W-Well, you didn't realize it, either!
I mean, the time we spent
together is different.
What's wrong with your eyes?
Do you even have any?
Oh, shut up!
Yeah, so I'm oblivious and blind.
I'm arrogant and have an ugly personality!
Well, she took that quite personally.
So in that regard...
Why did you make that request earlier?
Request? When did I ever
request anything from you?
You did! You asked me to go out with you!
Go out with the real...
Go out with me instead!
That's the "request" you're talking about?
Did I really say that?
Er, that was just... me going
with the flow... or something.
All right.
Huh?
If you're that insistent,
I don't mind accepting your request.
Wait, does that mean...
I'm saying that I'll go out with you.
Huh?
Kane-chama!
Hey.
Wh-What happened to your face?
I was punched. Like, "wham!"
What? But that's so mean!
I know, right? He didn't hold back, either.
He really is awful.
Kane-chama?
Are you crying, Kane-chama?
I guess they all know now!
Honestly, I feel great!
Kane-chama?
I wonder what I should do now.
Maybe I'll have him take
some responsibility, too.
Responsibility?
Please quiet down!
Don't forget.
You're the one who asked me out,
meaning I have the upper hand here.
Are you listening to me?
O-Of course I am!
Onii-chan!
I keep telling you dinner's ready!
Your miso soup is gonna get cold.
Onii-chan!
Oof. Sad.
Onii-chan?
M-Mom! I think Onii-chan just died!
M-Makabe-senpai...
I love you.
How many does that make this month?
Do they all just want to
find someone by Christmas?
Aren't you cold with your
legs exposed like that?
I just want to get back to class...
I was wondering i-if you'd go out with...
I'm sorry, I can't.
I see...
I'm trying to act as natural as
possible and seem apologetic
so they won't feel so bad...
I promise it's not you.
I guess the rumors are true, then.
Huh?
So Adagaki-senpai, who hates men,
finally fell for Makabe-senpai...
I'm not sure if "fell for" is the right term...
But it's true that we're going out.
I see. I guess you're happy now.
Y-Yes...
But I...
I don't care if I'm your number two!
What?!
Please let me have some of your time, too!
Uh, wait... I don't know about that!
Oh, I know. Here!
Just think of this as me!
Vitamin B12
Vitamin C
Amino Acids
1% Juice
Bye!
Senpai!
Senpai's leftovers...
Not bad!
Man... The ones who keep
approaching me lately are intense.
Well, you two just formed a superstar couple.
That doesn't happen often.
Most of the young ladies and gentlemen
are crying themselves to sleep at night.
If they aren't, they're probably
coming after you now.
That must be rough.
Don't have too much fun with all this,
Fujinomiya-san. It doesn't conce—
It doesn't concern me?
I might be one of the ones
crying herself to sleep each night.
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
I know there's been a lot going on,
so I had to put this off, but I...
No, it's not like I wanted to hear an answer.
What do you mean?
Well, considering the circumstances...
We don't know what's going
to happen, so we can hold off.
Yes, that's for the best.
So you're just going to enjoy this mess.
Oh, my.
Considering the circumstances, huh?
So, Pig's Foot...
I need you to save Aki-sama.
Go out with the real...
Go out with me instead!
I'm saying that I'll go out with you.
So I guess that means Fujinomiya-san
sees through everything.
Yeah, we may be going out, but...
I mean... I was the one who asked her out.
I can't go back on that now.
You have a new message.
Cruel Princess
Go buy me
some bread for lunch.
Go buy me some bread for lunch.
Wow, she pisses me off.
God, I don't want to go into that mess.
Hurry up. If you don't, I'll shrivel up
and die like some zebra on the savanna.
Cruel Princess
Hurry up!
If you don't, I'll shrivel up and die
like some zebra on the savanna.
Zebras don't eat croquette buns!
Rising Sun!
Ma'am, can I get three
explosive croquette buns and...
You need to speak up!
Why don't you yell like you did the other day?
Huh?
What?!
If you cause that much of a ruckus,
it'll draw more attention
to me that I don't need.
Well, I mean, obviously I'm surprised.
I heard you pretty much ghosted everyone
after that, so you just popping up was...
The school took pity on me and let me work.
Because I'm flat broke.
Flat broke? What do you mean?
This was all part of my plan. "Plan F."
F?
F as in fishing.
What? Fishing?
I was going to act like I was
you from eight years ago
and fish financial support
from the Adagaki family.
Financial support... Why would you do that?
I've got a lot going on.
Well, that plan gloriously
fell apart, didn't it?
With you punching me and all.
Well, I didn't know you were a girl.
So I managed to pay back all the expenses.
For Sale
I sold off our mansion.
What?! You sold your home?!
Are you gonna be okay?
Honestly, I feel relieved.
I was pushing myself way too hard
to make my family look good.
And I had to keep lying to
people around me to do so.
Now I just get to enjoy myself.
I get to live in an apartment
with nothing tying me down.
I promised my little sister we'd go to a
bathhouse once she's out of the hospital.
Gasou...
I don't have to force myself to
act like a guy anymore, either.
I see...
It's true that I was pissed when she used
my name and tried to act like me...
And I was wondering what
happened after all that.
I'm glad.
I guess that might be weird coming from me.
Yeah, it's pretty weird.
But to think that the bullied, chubby little
Masamune-kun would change so much.
Wh-What? Now you're gonna threaten me?
No. Honestly, I sorta want you
to take responsibility for this.
Responsibility?
Make me your wife.
What?!
I thought about it and realized
that you're pretty rich yourself,
and you get good grades,
so you've also got a pretty promising future.
See? I guess I don't have to give up just yet.
Nope! Not happening! Do you hear yourself?!
I'm already dating someone, anyway!
Why are you taking this so seriously?
Wait, what?! It was a joke?!
You really just said,
"I'm already dating someone!"
You mean...
Aki-chan, don't you?
Oh, never mind!
Man, you really are strange, Masamune-kun.
Upsy-daisy...
I wonder if this thing really works...
What are you doing?
Makabe!
T-Took you long enough!
Did you actually go to Africa or something?
A-A lot happened, okay?
What?
A stove?
Yoshino found it back there.
I thought I might be able to use it.
You just want it out here? Hup.
Th-Thank—
I'll set it in the center.
Huh?!
Uh, sure...
The only problem with
this shed is that it's cold.
Are you planning to spend
the long winter in here?
Shut up and just give me the food you bought!
Yeah, yeah, Zebra-sama.
Man, is it that hard to just say thank you?
Explosive
Croquette Bun
O-Of course I can! I was just about to
say it! It's the right thing to do!
Uh-huh...
Here. You can have this.
Good job. Here's your treat.
Explosive
Croquette Bun
Having fried food right now might be, uh...
And you can have a rice ball, too.
Do you want salmon or cod roe?
I have my own thing, okay?!
That's not enough! You need to eat more!
The old Masamune was much rounder!
We should get some
donuts after school, too.
Also, you need to try this new drink.
Wait, wait, wait!
What is this plan of fattening me up again?
I got skinny so I could get revenge on you!
Though it was all a misunderstanding...
Not like I can say any of that.
The new one is apparently
white chocolate whipped cream.
Let's go right after school, and...
Um...
Sorry, I'm gonna pass.
Huh?
Er, I mean...
But how am I supposed to reward you, then?
No, really!
Just the sentiment...
is more than enough.
D-Don't touch me so casually!
S-Sorry! I wasn't thinking!
I got some kerosene from the janitor's office.
Well, bye!
Man, I panicked.
But why the heck was I panicking?
The one who called me
Pig's Foot wasn't Adagaki Aki.
And Master feels bad about it.
I don't have anyone to hate anymore...
Huh?
U-Um...
Master!
Master and I used to come here pretty often.
We'd talk about the details of our plan...
Was that the tree she
hung me upside-down from?
No. It's the next one over.
I'll do it again if you'd like.
I'll pass, thanks.
How did our conversation turn into this?
You're right.
We should get to the point.
Y-Yeah, I was just wondering
how you're doing lately.
No problems?
No. Nothing.
That's good.
It's because you didn't tell
Aki-sama what I did.
I mean, what would be the point?
I almost let slip to her that I tried
to get close to her for revenge.
Most importantly...
I couldn't blame you,
since you continued to feel bad.
Despite everything that happened,
I'm going out with her.
That part is on track.
I see. So everything's okay, then.
Well, actually...
I'm sorry! It's not okay!
Going out with someone is super hard!
Honestly, Pig's Foot...
Yes, you can call me a pig all you want!
Considering she clearly
wants me to become a pig!
What am I supposed to do now, Master Koiwai?
Please show me some mercy!
I beg of you! Koiwai-sama!
This is your last bonus.
Aki-sama's birthday is the 24th of this month.
Christmas Eve!
She'll be really happy if
you celebrate it with her.
I see! Thank you, Master! No, my goddess!
Also...
I'm going to stop making contact
with you like this.
Huh?